[{"answer": "He's pretty good, that's the weird part", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No.   Do I want to", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm a married woman", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Meaning I'm not looking for company", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "And how, happy is that", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "How'd you know", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "How does Pinehaven look", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What is your name, anyway", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Come on! It's been three days.      I want to see you", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm going.   I'm going", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It's not too late to back out", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It's not you, it's us. I'm sure I'll make some mistake", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes it is", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " They asked me to r", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That's it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Interesting choice of phrase", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hey, that's an idea. Ask her where the glasses are, where she did it... Anything else I'm forgetting, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I swear to you, I don't.     What's wrong with you", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I must have missed them. I wasn't looking for them. I thought they were on my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Listen to me. That's why I fired her. After my friend's death she started acting strange. She was always watching me, listening to my calls", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, my friend, not with her I wasn't. I could tell there was a difference. Maybe she know about us. Maybe she wants something", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah.    You always run this late", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What's in that place", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You're some kind of health nut.  my friend smokes that same brand. I noticed that", "docId": "Body-Heat.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend, your lawyer is present", "qsentId": 28}]